coltsathletics.org 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy - VNN

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or mailing address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

To utilize the services of our trusted third-party service providers and partners, you may be asked to provide your credit card information and other personal information as necessary.

Our technology may employ tracking pixels. A tracking pixel is a piece of code embedded on a web page that collects information about visitors’ behavior on that web page. The tracking pixel can either be provided by the advertising channels, affiliate networks or by Varsity News Network, LLC. The tracking pixel may include a command to create cookies.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the sites of VNN partner schools.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users of sites of VNN partner schools based on their visit to the sites of VNN partner schools and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our site (we continually strive to improve our site offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To administer a VNN contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 

To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the sites of VNN partner schools. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users of sites of VNN partner schools based on their visit to the sites of VNN partner schools and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Do we share your information with third-parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our site, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  Those trusted third-party partners may:

  * Provide you and our partner schools with various services
  * Provide database maintenance and security
  * Help us manage transactions
  * Help us process and fulfill orders or requests
  * Create an account on such third-party site to provide various services to you
  * Allow a “single-sign-on” where after you log-in to VNN you will not have to log-in to our partner websites

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**User Consent and Terms of Service**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy and our [terms of service](http://vnnsports.net/user-agreement/).  

Please visit our [Terms of Service](http://vnnsports.net/user-agreement/) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our site at http://vnnsports.net/user-agreement.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our site. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

VNN tracks its Users over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. 

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our site, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

VNN, Inc

ATTN: Privacy Officer

678 Front St NW, Suite 300

Grand Rapids, MI 49504

connect@vnnsports.net
